Strut like you mean it
The Cheetah Girls 2 is a family, comedy, drama film directed by Kenny Ortega.
Best friends Galleria, Chanel, Dorinda, and Aqua, A.K.A.
the girl band "The Cheetahs," get the opportunity of a lifetime when they strut their
way to Barcelona, Spain, to perform in an international music festival.
Along the way, the "amigas Cheetahs" learn that, although their paths are not
the same, they are lucky to have one another for the journey.
Galleria Garibaldi, played by Raven-Symoné.
Chanel Simmons, played by Adrienne Bailon-Houghton.
Dorinda Thomas, played by Sabrina Bryan.
Aqua Walker, played by Kiely Williams.
Ángel, played by Peter Vives.
Marisol Durán, played by Belinda.
The Cheetah Girls 2 is a 2006 American musical
comedy film directed by Kenny Ortega.
It is the sequel to The Cheetah Girls (2003).
The plot follows the talented teen quartet who take a whirlwind tour
of Spain to pursue their dreams of pop superstardom.
The film's premiere received the highest ratings of all Disney Channel Movies at its time, a total of
over 8.1 million viewers, beating the previous record holder, Cadet Kelly (7.8 million).
The Cheetah Girls 2 is also the highest-rated film of The Cheetah Girls trilogy.
The Cheetah Girls 2 was the highest-rated Disney Channel Original Movie of 2006 and, as of
2024, is the joint-eighth-highest-rated Disney Channel Original Movie of all time.
The Cheetah Girls 2 was also the last The Cheetah
Girls film to feature Raven-Symoné.
The film explores themes of spain, based on novel or book,
music festival, sequel, summer vacation.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.